<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>shiny on Aurélien Callens</title>
    <link>https://aureliencallens.github.io/tags/shiny/</link>
    <description>Recent content in shiny on Aurélien Callens</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>aurelien.callens@gmail.com (Aurelien Callens)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>aurelien.callens@gmail.com (Aurelien Callens)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aureliencallens.github.io/tags/shiny/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Can R and Shiny make me a better fisherman? Part 4</title>
      <link>https://aureliencallens.github.io/2022/04/12/r-shiny-fishing-part4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>aurelien.callens@gmail.com (Aurelien Callens)</author>
      <guid>https://aureliencallens.github.io/2022/04/12/r-shiny-fishing-part4/</guid>
      <description>In this post, I explore the data I have collected during the last year with the updated version of the application (presented here). This quick exploratory analysis is performed with two packages I really enjoy: Plotly and shiny.
For reminder, my new application store the data in three csv files. The first one contains variables related to the fishing conditions. The second one contains information about my catches and finally the third one contains information about the characteristics of the lures I used during the session.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can R and Shiny make me a better fisherman? Part 3</title>
      <link>https://aureliencallens.github.io/2021/06/01/r-shiny-fishing-part3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>aurelien.callens@gmail.com (Aurelien Callens)</author>
      <guid>https://aureliencallens.github.io/2021/06/01/r-shiny-fishing-part3/</guid>
      <description>In this previous post, I presented the shiny application I developed to record data about my fishing session. In today’s post, I will present briefly the changes and updates I made to improve the application. Here are the main changes :
 Weather API: the API I was using (Dark Sky) stopped furnishing free data. I changed for Openweathermap and I needed to update the functions to gather the same information as before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can R and Shiny make me a better fisherman? Part 1</title>
      <link>https://aureliencallens.github.io/2020/09/12/r-shiny-fishing-part1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>aurelien.callens@gmail.com (Aurelien Callens)</author>
      <guid>https://aureliencallens.github.io/2020/09/12/r-shiny-fishing-part1/</guid>
      <description>My favorite hobby, in addition to R coding of course, is fishing. Most of the time, I am fishing European sea bass (Dicentrarchus labrax) in estuaries. The sea bass is a predatory fish that has a broad range of preys: crabs, sand eels, prawns, shrimps and other fish. To catch these predators, I don’t use live baits, I prefer to use artificial lures that imitate a specific prey.
In theory, it is quite easy to catch a fish:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
